{
    "subject": "resource/Nathan_Oman",
    "predicate": "ontology/almaMater",
    "object": "resource/Harvard_Law_School",
    "human_readable": "Nathan Oman attended Harvard Law School.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9728989601135254,
            "question": "What level of education did Nathan Oman obtain at Harvard Law School?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9541929364204407,
            "question": "Where did Nathan Oman attend law school?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9446682929992676,
            "question": "Which university is known for its law school that Nathan Oman attended?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9198763370513916,
            "question": "What is the name of the law school that Nathan Oman attended?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8443976640701294,
            "question": "Can you name any famous alumni of Harvard Law School besides Nathan Oman?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7821344137191772,
            "question": "What type of institution did Nathan Oman attend?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6595755219459534,
            "question": "Is Nathan Oman a lawyer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5241143107414246,
            "question": "What are some of the areas of law that are taught at Harvard Law School?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4050922393798828,
            "question": "What field of study is associated with Harvard Law School?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35829758644104004,
            "question": "Is Harvard Law School considered prestigious?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Nathan Oman attended Harvard Law School.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5297_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What field of study is associated with Harvard Law School?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5297_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of the areas of law that are taught at Harvard Law School?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5297_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Nathan Oman a lawyer?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5297_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5297_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5297_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5297_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5297_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5297_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5297_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5297_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5297_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5297_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5297_78.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nNone of the documents mention Nathan Oman attending Harvard Law School.  They state he is a professor at William & Mary Law School. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nThe reason for this answer is that none of the documents mention Nathan Oman attending Harvard Law School. In fact, one document mentions him as a professor at William and Mary Law School, but does not mention his attendance at any other law school."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"no\"}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided documents do not mention anything about Nathan B. Oman attending Harvard Law School. All the information given pertains to his current position as Rollins Professor of Law at William and Mary Law School, his work in contract law and Mormon legal history, and his religious affiliation with the Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints (Mormon). There is no mention of his educational background beyond his current role."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "There is no information provided in the context that suggests Nathan Oman attended Harvard Law School.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "None of the provided context mentions Nathan Oman attending Harvard Law School.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The context information does not mention Nathan Oman attending Harvard Law School. In fact, one of the contexts mentions him as a professor at William & Mary Law School, and another one mentions him speaking at the University of Houston Law Center, but there's no mention of him attending Harvard Law School.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information provided does not mention Nathan Oman attending Harvard Law School. The details focus on his position at William and Mary Law School, his expertise in contract law and Mormon legal history, and his involvement in various academic discussions and activities. There is no evidence supporting the claim that he attended Harvard Law School.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}